Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/travis-phang-jun-ming-249283181 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Sales & Marketing
Sales Presentations
Marketing Communications Planning

Languages

Mandarin, Cantonese (Native or Bilingual)

English (Native or Bilingual)
Malay (Native or Bilingual)

Travis Phang Jun Ming

Sales Executive

Selangor

Summary

"Hard work beats talent when talent fails to work hard"

Accomplished Sales & Marketing person with 3 years of experience in consistently promoting the brand and representing company values in all business interactions. Self-motivated with proficiency in expanding network connections, introducing products and pricing models and developing pipeline and territory to drive revenue.

Experience

89 Machinery Sales Executive September 2019 - July 2020 (11 months)

- -Develop new revenue opportunities and closing deals in assigned territory.
- -Monitored customer buying trends, market conditions and competitor actions to adjust strategies and achieve sales goals.
- -Contacted key accounts regularly and achieved high satisfaction scores by routinely re-assessing needs and resolving conflicts.
- -Worked with clients to find solutions according to specific needs and budgets and grew customer base through excellent services.

Universal Edu Group Marketing Executive November 2017 - August 2019 (1 year 10 months) Selangor, Malaysia

- -Built brand awareness and generated leads while managing internal and external marketing campaigns and programs.
- -Created and manage social media content to retain members and attract new followers.
- -Created high-impact messaging or content for all marketing media such as brochure, banner, booklet and etc.
- -Successfully to recruit & enroll more than 250 students continuously per year

Kein Hing Industry Sdn. Bhd. Production Planner February 2017 - May 2017 (4 months) Selangor, Malaysia

-Production management by ensuring and maintaining the flow of the material replenishment, smoothing the process time of the production as well as auditing the whole production process from replenish the raw material to the finish goods.

Education

Tunku Abdul Rahman University College Bachelor's degree of Business (HONS), International Business (2014 - 2017)